{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Front \u0026 Back Yard Landscaping Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40318/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40318,"taskName":"Landscape - Install Landscaping for Yard or Garden","taskDescription":"Landscape Yard or Gardens","xmTaskDescriptor":"Front \u0026 Back Yard Landscaping Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":145,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"landscaping yard xeriscaping gardening planting","textMessagingName":"Landscape","rolloverLongDesc":"Done once in a few years. Requires extensive understanding of plants \u0026 their water \u0026 soil needs. Usually handled by full service landscaping firms or professional gardeners.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes planning, bed definition, planting, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Landscape Yard or Gardens.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Yard \u0026 Garden Landscaping \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Front \u0026 Back Yard Installation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Landscaping for Yard or Garden Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Landscape - Install Landscaping for Yard or Garden","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Landscape Project","urlName":"Landscape-Install-Landscaping-for-Yard-or-Garden","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Yard \u0026 Garden Landscaping Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Backyard, Front Yard Installation","searchKeywords":"landscaping,yard,xeriscaping,gardening,planting,tree,plant,xeroscaping,xeroscape,xeriscape,garden,landscape,installation, mulch, mulching, ground, cover, rubber mulch, recycled mulch","emcCategoryOid":-12046,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":616,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40318/":{"taskOID":40318,"originalTaskOID":40318,"setID":616,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5431,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4051,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need design/plant suggestions","answerDisplayText":"Need design/plant suggestions","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2935,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Have a basic idea of what I want","answerDisplayText":"Have a basic idea of what I want","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Have professional drawings already","answerDisplayText":"Have professional drawings already","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1148,"questionDisplayText":"Landscaping to be installed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select what will be included in your landscaping project.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5987,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sprinkler system","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2841,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grass","answerDisplayText":"Grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5936,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Special planting area/Garden","answerDisplayText":"Special planting area/Garden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6492,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Trees/Shrubs","answerDisplayText":"Trees/Shrubs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2076,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7111,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wooden structures (deck, gazebo, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Wooden structures (deck, gazebo, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1564,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Concrete flatwork (patio, walkway, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Concrete flatwork (patio, walkway, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3758,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Masonry (brick and/or stone work)","answerDisplayText":"Masonry (brick and/or stone work)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3456,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Landscape lighting","answerDisplayText":"Landscape lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4727,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Play area","answerDisplayText":"Play area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4791,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Pool/Spa","answerDisplayText":"Pool/Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6859,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Water feature","answerDisplayText":"Water feature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6117,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Storage shed","answerDisplayText":"Storage shed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11225,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Xeriscape","answerDisplayText":"Xeriscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5433,"questionDisplayText":"Areas to be Landscaped","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which areas do you want to be landscaped? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard(s)","answerDisplayText":"Side yard(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3014,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hillside","answerDisplayText":"Hillside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5431,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4051,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need design/plant suggestions","answerDisplayText":"Need design/plant suggestions","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2935,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Have a basic idea of what I want","answerDisplayText":"Have a basic idea of what I want","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Have professional drawings already","answerDisplayText":"Have professional drawings already","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4051,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need design/plant suggestions","answerDisplayText":"Need design/plant suggestions","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2935,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Have a basic idea of what I want","answerDisplayText":"Have a basic idea of what I want","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2940,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Have professional drawings already","answerDisplayText":"Have professional drawings already","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1148,"questionDisplayText":"Landscaping to be installed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select what will be included in your landscaping project.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5987,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sprinkler system","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2841,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grass","answerDisplayText":"Grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5936,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Special planting area/Garden","answerDisplayText":"Special planting area/Garden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6492,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Trees/Shrubs","answerDisplayText":"Trees/Shrubs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2076,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7111,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wooden structures (deck, gazebo, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Wooden structures (deck, gazebo, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1564,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Concrete flatwork (patio, walkway, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Concrete flatwork (patio, walkway, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3758,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Masonry (brick and/or stone work)","answerDisplayText":"Masonry (brick and/or stone work)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3456,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Landscape lighting","answerDisplayText":"Landscape lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4727,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Play area","answerDisplayText":"Play area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4791,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Pool/Spa","answerDisplayText":"Pool/Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6859,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Water feature","answerDisplayText":"Water feature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6117,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Storage shed","answerDisplayText":"Storage shed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11225,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Xeriscape","answerDisplayText":"Xeriscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5987,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sprinkler system","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2841,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grass","answerDisplayText":"Grass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5936,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Special planting area/Garden","answerDisplayText":"Special planting area/Garden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6492,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Trees/Shrubs","answerDisplayText":"Trees/Shrubs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2076,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Drainage system","answerDisplayText":"Drainage system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7111,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wooden structures (deck, gazebo, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Wooden structures (deck, gazebo, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1564,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Concrete flatwork (patio, walkway, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Concrete flatwork (patio, walkway, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3758,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Masonry (brick and/or stone work)","answerDisplayText":"Masonry (brick and/or stone work)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3456,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Landscape lighting","answerDisplayText":"Landscape lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4727,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Play area","answerDisplayText":"Play area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4791,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Pool/Spa","answerDisplayText":"Pool/Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6859,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Water feature","answerDisplayText":"Water feature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6117,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Storage shed","answerDisplayText":"Storage shed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11225,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Xeriscape","answerDisplayText":"Xeriscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5433,"questionDisplayText":"Areas to be Landscaped","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which areas do you want to be landscaped? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard(s)","answerDisplayText":"Side yard(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3014,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hillside","answerDisplayText":"Hillside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard(s)","answerDisplayText":"Side yard(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3014,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hillside","answerDisplayText":"Hillside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}